<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Zombie Apocalypse Survival</string>

    <string name="title_activity_equipment">Equipment</string>

    <string name="IntroductionParagraph">

        The English word \"Zombie\" was first recorded in 1819, originating from the West African traditions of Haitian slaves. The first such stories involve people placed into long-term comas from various drugs, later seeming to "rise from the dead".
        \n\n
        <i>Frankenstein</i>, while not actually a zombie novel, influenced the genre by proposing a scientific rather than mystical origin. Lovecraft, Romero and Matheson were other authors who pioneered the zombie genre, with books like <i>I am Legend</i> and <i>The Last Man on Earth</i>.
        \n\n
        Romero\'s 1968 <i>Night of the Living Dead</i> was the first zombie film to achieve commercial success, spawning a huge genre, with 55 films released in just 2014.
        \n\n
        Today, zombies are largely depicted as hungry for human flesh or brains. One major theme of the genre is the "Zombie Apocalypse", showing the complete breakdown of society as a result of a viral zombie outbreak.

    </string>


    <string name="StrategyParagraph">

        Have a set of supplies readily accessible before the apocalypse starts, no matter wherever you are.
        \n
        Avoiding densely populated areas is a wise plan, but going too far into the wilderness will make scavenging for supplies difficult.
        \n
        Be ruthless but not needlessly antagonistic. Other survivors may be more willing to help as a result.


    </string>


    <string name="EquipmentParagraph">

        Everyone wants guns and chainsaws, but there are many more types of supplies which you will need to remain alive - and more importantly, not undead.
        \n\n
        To begin, you will definitely need water, preserved food and other consumables available to you when the apocalypse starts. Planning is vital for your survival.
        \n\n
        While shelter is nice, a tent is the last thing you should bring. It adds weight and takes too long to set up/take down.
        \n\n
        Basic medical supplies are also important. No sense in death due to a normal, non-zombie infection.
        \n\n
        A sharp-edged object (e.g. knife) will also be extremely important. Never know what you will need to cut up; zombies, food, competing survivors, etc.
        \n\n
        Binoculars, because generally you want to see the zombies before they see you.
        \n\n
        At night you will definitely need a flashlight, you do not want to get lost in the dark. Be careful when using it, however - It may draw attention to you!
        \n\n
        Other :
        \n
        \t1)Water Purifier - Do not want to drink dirty water
        \n
        \t2)Rope - just in case you want to setup traps or get to high places
        \n
        \t3)Fire Starter - Heat is important, do not need to worry about getting to cold


    </string>


    <string name="HotLine">Hot Lines</string>


    <string name="hotlines">

        For Emergencies: 555-6825
        \n
        For additional Questions: 559-4872
        \n
        For air support: 555-5555
        \n\n
        Need Supplies Fast? Call our 24/7 toll free number: 555-9887
        \n\n
        Want to Contact Mr. Paulson?
        \n
        Send a email to: brian.paulson@ww-p.org



    </string>


    <string name="meida">Coming Soon</string>

    <string name="strat">Strategy </string>

    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>

    <string name="title_activity_introduction">Introduction</string>

    <string name="title_activity_thingy">thingy</string>

</resources>
